meet again You wanna play
the music I'll give up no
one Open the world Let the
truth make a difference
You can't applaud yourself
Don't forget to game your world
I'll be so high-tension I can't let
you know I can't speak anymore Love me,
love me Go ahead and set
me down Love me heavy Creep
it Jar Love me Love me I'm so making my
day Show me! Show me! Thinking who Isek
,édit Don't
forget
to
Before he can activate his
technique, I have to beat him!
Sorry, but all acts of violence are
indefinitely prohibited in this space.
For both of us.
Both of us?
However, harmful remarks
are the exception.
Judge, ma 'am.
Please begin.
The defendant, Yuji Itadori, stands
accused of committing the following crime.
On July 16th, 2017,
the defendant entered Maji Vegas Pachinko
Parlor, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture,
despite being under the
legal age of 18 at the time.
Huh?
Within this domain, Judge Man knows all
who've entered and everything they've done.
But don't worry yourself too much.
That information has
never been shared with me.
The verdict will be decided solely
by the arguments we present today.
With the exception of this evidence.
Huh?
Where'd you get that from?
This is the evidence Judge Man
provided and submitted for this case.
There is no guarantee that this will confirm
the charges alleged against you today.
Nevertheless, it will
remain a secret to you.
Knowing that, you must
now present your argument.
Your goal is to clear suspicion and
win an innocent verdict from Judge Man.
A court trial technique?
That badge.
So he really was a defense lawyer.
But isn't he acting
like a prosecutor here?
Higuruma is a modern sorcerer.
This domain is like what
Tengen talked about.
Domains used to be a much
more standard skill set for
sorcerers to use against
their enemies in the past.
That's because they lacked the guaranteed
kill element that applies
to today's attacks.
Modern domains have become
guaranteed to be deadlier.
The guarantee was that
users' techniques would
without question hit their
target within the domain.
That used to be the commonplace
function of domains in the past.
By focusing too hard on
the guaranteed kill aspect,
sorcerers raised the bar on
requirements for constructing a domain,
making it a more advanced skill,
with fewer practitioners every day.
That means this domain
is founded on packs.
It prevents lethal use,
prohibits physical harm, and it
requires some explanation of its rules.
You get one chance to make a statement.
The same goes for me.
After your statement, I will get to
make my rebuttal using this evidence.
And then, Judge Mann will announce his
verdict in accordance with the six codes.
What happens if I'm found guilty?
Unfortunately, I am under no
obligation to answer that question,
but I will at least tell you this.
After all, you have rights.
If guilty, you have three options.
Silence, confession, or denial.
Your denial may include false statements.
You mean I can lie?
In a court of law?
If everyone told the truth in court,
there would be no need for trials.
Now, make your argument.
Judge Man is not very patient.
I did go to that pachinko parlor.
And I totally played some games.
I think I even won some.
I can't avoid lying if I still
want to claim my innocence.
So naturally, what I
need to consider is...
what could be in that evidence?
There is no guarantee that this will confirm
the charges alleged against you today.
One,
if that evidence doesn't prove
I entered the pachinko parlor,
I just need to deny it or remain silent.
No!
Two, if the evidence only
proves I entered the parlor,
can I say it was for another reason?
I just went in to use their bathroom.
But if the evidence
turns out to be a bust,
then I might be digging my own grave by
admitting I definitely entered the parlor.
Three,
if the evidence proves I not only entered
the parlor, but also played the games,
I'm basically screwed.
I regret it!
But what if confessing
lightens my sentence?
Wait, does this court even
offer lighter punishments?
I confess.
The fact is, I entered
the pachinko parlor.
But it was only because I needed to poop.
Then I had to use their bathroom.
Is that so?
I'm going with option two.
I don't know if this court
accepts extenuating circumstances,
but this excuse is the most relatable.
Let's hope.
Now it's my turn.
Let's take a look at the evidence.
This is security camera footage from
the antique shop near Maji, Vegas.
The store has an ATM which captured
this image on the day in question.
Note how striking the
resemblance, both face and build,
are a perfect match to Yuji Itadori.
And since he just admitted
to entering the parlor,
this photo makes it clear
that his excuse about
needing the bathroom isn't
worth a roll of toilet paper.
One can thus reason that
despite being underage,
Itadori entered the parlor with
the intent to play pachinko.
So then you're saying that's a crime?
The parlor had clear
posted signs explicitly
prohibiting minors from
entering the premises.
You are charged with criminal trespassing.
Article 130 of the Penal Code.
The Businesses Affecting
Public Morals Regulation Act.
But it doesn't punish minors.
No fair.
You set me up.
There was no way for me
to talk my way out of it.
Should I have gone with Option 3?
What are you talking about?
Japan prohibits gambling.
So, parlors and ATMs are
separate legal entities.
Sometimes multiple
parlors even share ATMs.
You were only on trial for
entering into Maji Vegas.
All you needed to say was, I'm sorry,
but I don't recognize that parlor.
And that way, you can deny the
charge without lying to me.
Wait, we haven't heard the verdict yet.
Guilty.
Confiscation.
We're back where we started?
Now I've been declared guilty.
I don't feel any different.
He's careful!
What a weapon!
Not only can he make it
appear and disappear at will,
he can alter its size too?
Wait, something's wrong.
You're pretty tough.
At least I still have that.
Because I can't control my cursed energy.
Law Apprenticeship Period 59.
Iwate Bar Association's
Hiromi Higuruma, age 36.
He easily cleared all obstacles,
like the entry exam to Tokyo
University's School of Law and the
old bar exam that preceded the
institution of the law school system.
To Higuruma,
it was all a matter of simply
inputting and outputting the necessary
knowledge that was needed for each
individual task in front of him.
His peers whispered in the hallways behind
his back that he was
a genius of some kind.
And yet,
the gem that shone brightest
from his unlimited potential
was his overwhelming talent
as a Jujutsu sorcerer.
This technique came with
his domain by default,
but through analyzing his domain,
he also learned the fundamentals
of how barriers work.
Then, working backwards from barriers,
he intuitively gathered how to manipulate
cursed energy for physical enhancement.
And within 12 days of
awakening as a sorcerer,
his powers had grown to
match those of a grade 1.
Before entering the colony,
Higuruma exercised many cursed spirits,
and he struck down over 20 players who
had the misfortune of attacking him first.
You lost the ability to
control Cursed Energy?
Didn't you take it from me?
The penalty of confiscation
makes it temporarily
impossible to use one's Cursed Technique.
So I'm guessing you've never had
a cursed technique to begin with?
That must be why the penalty switched
to blocking the use of cursed energy.
Coincidentally,
confiscation is generally a supplementary
sentence never imposed on its own.
It's terrifying to think
about how good he is.
How can he hold his own against
me without cursed energy?
He's using his natural physical
prowess, not his might as a sorcerer.
He must have incredibly
high physical durability.
When sorcerers lose the
use of their technique,
they often struggle with
basic Cursed Energy control.
Their instincts probably dull
over the many long years,
but the complete inability to use Cursed
Energy is even more disadvantageous.
Yet he can still fight this
well under these circumstances.
My first strike would have usually
settled the battle against most foes.
If I'm not careful, I'll trip me up.
I'll crush him with my full might.
You're incredible.
It's like I'm fighting some
kind of unbreakable doll.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
How long will this last?
I need my cursed energy.
Come back to me.
He's got such a strong ability.
There must be something I can do.
There's something that puts
Higuruma at a disadvantage!
Think!
Think? Think!
A technique for court trials.
Trials!
Higuruma!
I want a retrial!
You figured it out.
That was close.
I get a second trial, right?
As long as the targeted defendant
never actually admitted their guilt,
even after having previously been found
guilty and subjected to
penalty by Judge Man?
they are entitled to
demand up to two retrials.
Judge Man is incapable of
refusing such a request.
I demand a do-over!
The court calls Yuji Itadori.
You stand accused of mass murder in
Shibuya on the night of Halloween,
October City, 2018.
Yeah, I killed all of them.
I'm not going to deny it.
Guilty! Confestation!
Death Penalty!
Higuruma.
Yoshizawa.
I've already submitted the proposal,
if that's what you're here about.
No, I'm not here about that.
I took a look at the documents.
They're wonderful.
Good enough as is for the
judge to use in his sentencing.
You wanted to be either a public prosecutor
or a defense lawyer, is that right?
Yes.
Consider something else.
How would you feel about
becoming a judge instead?
The heaviest sentence Judge
Man can impose on the guilty
is confiscation accompanied
by the death penalty.
Confiscation makes it impossible for
the guilty party to use their technique,
or in Itadori's case,
control his cursed energy.
As prosecutor, Higuruma is
granted the executioner's sword.
Anyone cut by the
Executioner's sword will,
without exception, meet
their untimely death.
Being empathetic to another person's
feelings means understanding their weakness.
The weakness of victims.
The weakness of criminals.
Day after day after day.
I was so fed up with everything.
So ugly.
That's what I started to think every time
I tried to help someone
who needed a break.
Just like you, Itadori!
All people are weak and ugly!
No matter how much you long
for them to have noble souls!
There's nothing for you down that path!
The darkness before you is just that!
Even if you shine a light on it,
you'll just find blinding nothingness!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to become a judge.
I see.
May I ask why you feel this way?
All people are weak and ugly.
I'm not interested in promotions,
so I'm not cut out for it.
However, at the time, at
least up until that moment,
I believed that the very
depravity which no other
creatures possessed was
meant to be cherished.
Why?
Yuji Itadori, why did
you admit your guilt?
The evidence that Judge Man
submits is shared with the sorcerer
before it is revealed to the defendant
during the course of the trial.
The evidence Judge-Man provided was about
the demon harbored inside you, Sukuna!
You didn't kill them!
So why? Why?!
Uh, hey.
Penal Code Article 39, Clause 1.
Being deprived of either
sound judgment or control
of one's actions qualifies
as non-compost mentis.
That night in Shibuya, Sukuna took
control of your body, didn't he?
How do you know about Sukuna?
In other words, you lacked
control of your actions.
You didn't voluntarily
surrender control either.
And so, you're innocent.
You've committed no crime.
Regardless of all that,
it's still my fault.
Because I was too weak to stop him.
I see.
Igaruma, why did you release
your technique just now?
I wanted to return to my roots.
Itadori, there may still be plenty of
people who are weak and ugly like you,
wandering around out there.
Put your shirt back on, then have a seat.
I'm giving you my hundred points.
Itadori, have you ever killed someone
by your own will and not a Sukuna?
I have.
I see.
Didn't it feel awful?
I'll
see
you
next time.
I don't know if it's not a war.
I don't know if it's all.
It's all for the end of the day.
I'm going to leave you here.
I don't want to lose you.
But I'm scared of it.
I'm going to lose you.
I'm going to get you.
but I'm not in the corner of my head.
I'm going to keep looking.
I'm going to take you.
Kogane, add a new rule.
Make possible the transfer
of points between players.
Of course,
this should count toward the change in
points mentioned in rule number eight.
Approved! Rule added.
Rule number ten.
Players are able to
transfer a number of points
of their choosing to
other players in the game.
Kogane, give one of my points to Itadori.
As you wish.
You have been granted one
point by Hiromi Higuruma.
Now neither of us will have to worry about
our techniques being stripped for 19 days.
Take care.
Higuruma, what are you planning to do now?
You could join us if you want.
We'd be stronger with your help.
My two remaining points
are from the judge and
prosecutor that I killed
before coming to Tokyo.
Once the barriers open up, I
think I might turn myself in.
Until then, I'll think
about what I should do next.
Besides, if I stay with you, I'm
likely to hate myself even more.
Sorry, I'm not criticizing you.
See you later.
Thank you.